import Question, { QuestionType } from '../models/Question';

const triviaQuestions: Question[] = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'Which animal represents Gryffindor house?',
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: ['Lion', 'Eagle', 'Badger', 'Snake'],
    answer: 0,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'What is a "Muggle"?',
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: [
      'A non-magical person from a magical family',
      'A magical person with only one magical parent',
      'A non-magical person from a non-magical family',
    ],
    answer: 2,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "True or false: Professor Dumbledore's spectacles are rectangular?",
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: ['True', 'False'],
    answer: 1,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'What do you say when you cast a Summoning Charm?',
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: ['Avis', 'Accio', 'Aparecium', 'Anapneo'],
    answer: 1,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: 'What colour is the Hogwarts Express?',
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: ['Indigo', 'Emerald', 'Scarlet', 'Green'],
    answer: 3,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "Whom do Harry, Ginny and Neville join in a Hogwarts Express compartment at the beginning of Harry's fifth year?",
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: ['Ron Weasley', 'Luna Lovegood', 'Remus Lupin', 'Cho Chang'],
    answer: 1,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: 'The Divination classroom is at the top of which Hogwarts tower?',
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: ['East', 'South', 'West', 'North'],
    answer: 3,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Hagrid's full title is Keeper of Keys at Hogwarts",
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: ['True', 'False'],
    answer: 1,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Who wrote the Hogwarts textbook 'A History of Magic'?",
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: [
      'Quentin Trimble',
      'Adalbert Waffling',
      'Bathilda Bagshot',
      'Arsenius Jiggle',
    ],
    answer: 2,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      'In his first class with Professor Slughorn, Harry wins a tiny glass bottle of which potion?',
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: ['Veritaserum', 'Polyjuice', 'Amortentia', 'Felix Felicis'],
    answer: 3,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      'True or False: The students and teachers from Beauxbatons and Durmstrang arrive at Hogwarts on Halloween.',
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: ['True', 'False'],
    answer: 1,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: 'How many broomsticks are flown in a full game of Quidditch?',
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: ['15', '14', '16', '267'],
    answer: 0,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: 'What type of creature is an Ashwinder',
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: ['Bird', 'Serpent', 'Dog', 'Fish'],
    answer: 1,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: 'What house was Moaning Myrtle sorted into?',
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: ['Ravenclaw', 'Gryfindor', 'Hufflepuff', 'Slytherin'],
    answer: 0,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "What number is Harry's vault at the Gringotts Wizarding Bank?",
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: ['713', '627', '711', '687'],
    answer: 3,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question:
      'On Harry’s first Hallowe’en at Hogwarts, who was responsible for the troll in the dungeon?',
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: ['Draco Malfoy', 'Hagrid', 'Quirrell', 'Snape'],
    answer: 2,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question:
      'In Chamber of Secrets book, why were Harry, Ron and Hermione not at the Hallowe’en feast?',
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: [
      'Trapped in convwersation Lockhart',
      'Nearly Headless Nick Party',
      'Detention',
      'They were with Hagrid in the forest',
    ],
    answer: 1,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: 'Who was Petrified by the Basilisk on Hallowe’en?',
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: [
      'Colin Creevey',
      'Justin Finch-Fletchery',
      'Mrs Norris',
      'Hermione',
    ],
    answer: 2,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: 'In Harry’s third year, who broke into Hogwarts on Hallowe’en?',
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: [
      'Peter Pettigrew',
      'Lord Voldemort',
      'Sirius Black',
      'Bellatriz Lastrange',
    ],
    answer: 2,
    status: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question:
      'On Hallowe’en night, who was the first Triwizard Champion to be announced?',
    type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE,
    options: ['Harry', 'Fleur', 'Cedric', 'Krum'],
    answer: 3,
    status: 0,
  },
];

export default triviaQuestions;
